What are your goals for your future activities?
What are your goals for future activities?
What are your goals for the future activities?
[QUESTION] What are your goals when promoting your future activities?
Thank you for watching
Thank you very much for watching.
Hello, everybody.
I'm here with someone.
How are you all? - I'm fine.
It's really bright here at 5:30, it's really bright outside.
It's bright outside, but it's a Sunday, so we're going to take it easy.
I hope you enjoy the show.
Are you guys watching?
They're watching like crazy.
865 people.
It's still light at 7 o'clock.
Nani.
Nah, nah, nah.
So cute!
Super cute
Super cute nails
So cute!
They talk about nails all the time.
Her nails are cuter.
Seriously cute
Cute.
I can see where you're coming from.
Yes, I know. So, let me start with a review of my recent activities.
I recently had a live performance at On Air Is at the end of last month.
Yay!
Yes, thank you very much to everyone who came.
Thank you very much.
This was the first live performance by the seven of us,
We had new costumes, new songs, etc. It was a lot of fun.
But it feels like it was a long time ago.
I think so. It feels like a long time ago.
A month ago.
Surprisingly recent, isn't it?
It hasn't been a month.
It hasn't passed yet.
It's the 28th.
So, last month, Ayaka Nation had a lot of help from everyone,
It's been going on since then.
It was Tsuchijima.
It was a week or two on Tsuchijima,
I had a lot of memories,
It was a while ago,
What?
The seven of us were doing the seven-person version of the dance, and the positions we were standing in, and all that.
It's already bad.
It's so bad.
I packed it all in with a lot of energy,
I'm not so good at it now,
I was just learning it,
I was just about to learn it,
I was on the edge.
If I was asked to do it now, I might not be able to go back,
I might not be able to go back.
There would be a clash.
But it's like that, really,
We're all about the live performance.
Everyone is here, here, here,
We all had our own events,
Yes, it was an intense May.
It was an intense month of May.
And Ayaka Nation, too,
Ayaka Nation, too,
One month ago.One month ago.
One month ago.
Still a month.
In about three days,
That's a month ago,
And that's just in the blink of an eye.
Right, everyone?
Nico,
You know..,
The girl who praised Aaryn.
Did you see that?
Yeah, just now,
You can catch the whole month,
I'll be streaming it throughout this month,
I hope you can see the great job everyone did,
I hope you will watch the victory,
I hope you will be able to see the victory.
Please do.
You went to see it, didn't you?
Ayaka Animal.
I went to see Day 1.
Yesterday, I was at Ayaka Animal Live.
Yes, you were. Thanks for your hard work.
Great, really.
I feel like Hari is at every Aaryn Live too.
I am seriously abusing food money.
Really.
But your impression of the live show has changed nails.
No, that's my first comment.
There are many more,
I'm going to make it sound like I'm related to them,
I tried to narrow down what I thought of the show, and here it is,
Your nails have changed.
I could tell even from the stage.
Mance can't get it off.
I couldn't get Mance.
But I recognized it right away.
I thought you were yawning.
What are you talking about?
I said, "Thanks for coming," and she said, "Your nails have changed.
Oh, oh.
Like, "Oh, wow.
It was kind of fun.
Oh, oh, oh.
That's right, for two days.
But you guys had a lot of relevees,
There was a lot of re-live, wasn't there?
Yes, there was.
It was flowing. It was a deck dock.
Something like colored pants.
That's right.
They did it on rainy days, too.
It was raining so hard.
We were soaked as if we had taken a bath.
It was fun, wasn't it? It was fun.
Nothing can compare to that wave of rain.
Once you experience it,
It's like everything is concentrated.
You can't see.
I can't see.
I can't even open my mouth.
You know what I mean?
If you've experienced that, you're not afraid of rain.
I wouldn't be afraid at all.
I enjoyed it.
Well, that's how it was.
June.
18th. The half-holiday is over.
So early.
But
I delivered it.
Here.
Since we went bowling.
I see.
Since takoyaki.
Oh, that's right.
Not a single takoyaki.
Not a single bowling.
Then bowling.
Pizza.
Bowling and pizza.
Takoyaki is studying and takoyaki.
He's eating something.
He's eating all the time.
So, that means you've been saying bowling recently, right?
That's right.
End of April?
Huh?
I'm going crazy.
It's going crazy.It's crazy, isn't it?
I feel like I've been seeing Namie members pretty much all the time lately.
Yes, that's right.
I've been seeing them a lot, so I feel like it's more than I should.
I have a lot of memories of the past.
I have a lot of memories.
I met Ailee a while ago.
Was it the first time we met after my birthday? I asked him.
Really? I didn't see her?
Did I say which one?
Yes, I did.
We've been seeing each other a lot lately.
I am very happy to see you.
I have an announcement to make.
Wow!
Hana-chan, don't stop!
They say they won't stop.
They're trying to make me stop every time.
Hana-chan.
That was Hana-chan, wasn't it?
You make me stop every time.
Because I'm Reri.
Every group has that.
At our work site...
That groove.
It started with the fans.
It wasn't something we said.
When we performed at the National
My perception is that
from there.
RENI-chan, don't stop! started there.
at that Kunitachi
At the end
Toward the torch stand
I'm going to walk from the main stage to the flower aisle.
We were supposed to walk one by one.
Reni-chan was the first to walk down the aisle.
She was the first one to walk down the aisle.
When we got to that point, the next person would go.
From our point of view
We were already planning to walk to our senses.
We didn't think anything of it.
From the fans' point of view
Reni-chan was the only one
It was like she was the only one walking.
Like it was the last show at the National Theater.
We were also a little bit in the middle of joy
and we're doing it with a "huh" look on our faces.
Don't stop!
You're right.
It's like the scene is...
It's like the scene has turned.
It's difficult.
But after that, the members just kept coming along.
Oh, I see.
They said it's going to be established that way.
Wow!
That's so interesting.
I think that's where it all started for me.
Maybe they're aware of that.
That's right.
You know, when you have feelings for me...
Don't stop.
I hear you're seriously going to stop.
It's true.
I'm serious.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
Again.
That feels good.
Yes, it does.
No, it's not... that's not why I'm calling it quits.
I'm not reporting that I'm quitting.
We went to Disneyland.
Yay!
Wow!
You know...
The other day...
Question Box
Disney
I got so many people asking me if I went to Disney in Namie.
I came too
But you know... everyone wanted to talk about it here.
I knew we were going to do this.
You didn't decide, right?
I kept my mouth shut.
Yay.
Yay.Yay.
Yes, that...
When Chi-chan was there...
We were talking about going to Disney.
Yes.
There's so many!
When I look at it like this
I don't know...
When I was here...
There were a lot of them.
I don't know if they're all here.
Who's not here?
It's like we're all here.
They're adults.
I thought maybe, worst-case scenario, they'd come back on their own.
So, you know, call him.
That's what it was like.
It was a lot.
You're sexy.
I was playing a sexy role.
I really stood out.
I've never been with this many people before.
It's my first time, too.
I'm going to tell you a little bit about Disney.
I thought I'd share with you guys.
I thought I'd share some memories with you.
I'd like to look back.
I've been waiting for you.
Oh, yeah.
I think you're probably right.
Why don't we start with...
Well, you know...
I've selected some photos of myself.
I'd like to introduce them to you.
Yes, sir.
This picture is
First of all
With Alice
with Matt Hatter
And here's the picture.
These two were long.
I'm not kidding.
They were really long.
I don't know.
They select someone from the other side.
And then they choose someone to take a picture with.
They would talk to us from the photo side of the picture.
I was looking at Alice, right?
I told her she was cute.
Usually the little girls were chosen.
And we were at the front of the line.
With Alice.
When the little girl was being given the award.
We were all looking at her and saying how cute she was.
Alice was given an ant skirt.
And then...
They're all wearing the same
They're all wearing the same catsuit.
They're all wearing the same catsuit, so I'm like, "Oseim!
"Next, next, next!
And the eight of us went...
We went and it was amazing.
We all had a tea party.
Alice invited us to a tea party.
Wither Oca.
In front of all the guests.
For about five minutes.
Super weak.
That was super weak.
People around us were taking pictures.
They took so many pictures of us.
They were taking pictures of us.
It was kind of awkward.
Everyone was getting their picture taken.
Everyone...
Matsubata...
holding a cup.
With Alice.
Make some tea.
Cheers.
One toast at a time.
It was a very long way down.
I was about the fourth person to see it go down.
I was thinking...
Really.
That's how we all had a tea party for about five minutes.
So I thought that would be the end of it,
I thought I couldn't take a picture, but I did,
Here's a picture from that time.Here's a picture from that time.
Alice was so energetic, like a tea party.
It was Parisian, wasn't it?
It was very Parisian.
Very much like a Tee Pee.
I felt like a tee-pee.
We did tee-pees and stuff.
It was very fun.
Matsubara was a little bit too,
I was a little bit scared.
They were doing "Rainbow Rainbow Rainbow.
It looked like fun.
He said that his ribbon would be rainbow tomorrow.
He said, "Tomorrow rainbow.
Tomorrow Rainbow.
Everyone didn't understand English, so all they could say was "yay.
It was not a conversation.
It was either "yay" or "whoo".
It was a real counterattack.
It was like a yo-yo.
That's how it was.
This is a memorable picture of the end of the tea party.
Then let's write obediently from here.
First, the first picture.
Eight pictures.
This one was really cute.
This was really cute.
Seriously, they were so cute.
Can you please stop taking pictures of the members who are not here?
I know that only Mr. Saeki is in charge of this group instead.
Is this provided by Kojima-san?
I did. I'm the one who provided it,
We were all standing in line for Splash Mountain,
The sun was shining pretty brightly,
We were expecting rain, right?
That's right.
But it turned out to be fine.
It was fine.
It had been raining for a week or two.
Just that day.
And the weather forecast.
The forecast was for rain from the moment we decided to meet on that day.
Everyone was checking the forecast all the time, and they thought it was going to rain,
I was 100% sure of the perfume.
I was like, "That's just the way it is at times.
I thought, "That's just the way it is.
Everyone was asleep.
Are you okay? If I can make it tomorrow afternoon, or tomorrow night.
They said, "I'll sleep it off.
But an hour or two later on the day of Disney, it was already amazing.
It was about 12 pallets.
It was after noon.
It was sunny.
The sun was shining, if you know what I mean.
That's right.
Then Chi-chan said she was going to reapply the suntanning dame, and took out the suntanning dame,
I thought she was reapplying something, so I watched her,
I was wondering what she was doing with her hands.
I wondered what she was doing.
Then she looked at me and showed me Mickey Mouse.
He was so cute.
So cute.
It was really fun.
It was amazing.
Is this your first time?
We saw it and decided to do it next time.
Let's do it next time.
We thought we learned something.
This is what makes you popular.
A popular girl.
I was determined to do it.
I have good drawing skills,
It's hard to call her Mickey,
It's definitely Ms. Furu, isn't it?
It's definitely Furu-san, isn't it?
A little bit,
He was really cute at that time.
The replacement Maru.
It's like he's wearing a tensen.
It's so cute that he's wearing a tensen.
What's this?
It was cute.
This is really cute.
There are soaps that come out like this, aren't there?
Yes, there is.
If you don't have it, you can't get a tan, or something like that.
It was amazing.
It was so cute.
I thought it was really cute.
I thought it was so cute.I thought it was so cute.
I was so taken by it.
I'm glad I put it in my favorite holder.
Sei-chan says it's cute because she does it.
What?
You're going to do it?
I'll definitely do it.
I'll show it to Arline.
Then Mickey is very realistic Mickey.
They don't do that.
There.
He did the rainy day stuff.
It's very realistic.
That's not it, that's not it.
You don't need drawing skills for this.
Seriously?
I used up all my suntan lotion.
It's sticky.
It's amazing, amazing, amazing.
It's so cute.
So cute.
It's a picture to remember.
Okay, let's continue.
Looks like fun.
What's this?
This is malicious.
Who is this?
That's me.
Paddy.
Yes, it's me. What is it?
It feels like it was raining.
I was looking around a little bit, and there were umbrellas here and there.
There were umbrellas,
I like to watch the members from the back,
I was following them from behind all the way to Disney,
The aura of everyone from the back was amazing,
It was like they were walking in a super hot group,
When I called out to them, they all turned their heads to look behind me,
It was weird that it was me.
It was weird to be me, but that's what I do.
We did the stick dance together.
Oh no.
One of us is leaking.
It's okay now.
It was too much fun.
Yuzu took this picture,
It's just a couple of pictures,
I'm looking like Kachi-chan.
Was there?
Yes, there was.
Chi-chan is surprised.
She's being photographed from behind, but I didn't think she'd be this surprised.
All the staff turned around.
I was happy to see that Disney has such cute angels.
They are super cute.
They stand out a lot.
And the clothes too,
We told them in advance what color they would wear.
That's right.
Did you decide to use any of the pastel colors in the catsuits this time?
Yes, that's right. We took the colors from there.
Harima insisted on pink.
No, no, no.
Haru-chan was.
Haruma said I must have pink.
No, no, no, no.
I didn't say that.
I feel bad about wearing pink.
Haruma said he would wear pink first.
She said it was non-negotiable.
I can't give in. I'm not.
It's too much. Hazui, hazu hazu.
Hazui hazu hazu hazu hazu.
Harima can't do such a wasteful thing of not using it.
I worked hard and bought it.
It was quite expensive.
You have to use it.
I asked the sales clerk about it.
I'm going to Disney, and she said she wanted pastel colors.
Did you ask her?
About eight of us are going, and I wanted to look cute.
I consulted with them about everything.
It was raining at first. It was wet.
I thought it was a gradation.
It was pink.
The bottom part was soaked too.
I had bought a gradient dress.
It was just a wet fall.
That's how I felt.That's how I feel.
But I really feel like I was walking in Disney once.
It was really once.
It really feels like it was once.
It's cute. When you look at it like this.
It's cute.
It looks like a girl's school. Super girls' school.
Cute.
Super cute.
It's adolescent.
It's true.
This scene is impossible.
That's it.
Next.
So cute!
I took a sneak peek.
Sneak peek.
She's cute.
Isn't she cute?
She's so cute.
This is too cute.
No matter where I take pictures, I get the feeling of her.
Yes, it does.
Is that so?
Really.
Yes, it's like a girlfriend.
Yes, it does.
She's super cute.
The image quality is a little rough.
It's like she must have taken it while she was moving.
It's so cute that I didn't really want to show it.
It's actually in my holder.
It's so cute.
You drank alcohol, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
A little bit. We're a team of sisters.
We all shared a little.
We're all in this group.
Sextuplets?
Sextuplets.
One line.
We were doing sextuplets.
I was drinking a drink I'd heard of.
I'm glad.
They don't know if it's good or not, so let Arline taste it first.
Where are you going?
Where are we going?
Here.
This is the place where they sell the booze, and there are several places in Disney that sell booze,
They're pretty aggressive here,
Really?
Yeah, they're really strong... or at least they taste like it.
They have some strong drinks, so I said, "I'll have a drink.
How are you doing?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
We passed it around together.
It was delicious.
Hurry up. Actually, Hana-chan and Yuzu, too.
All of us.
We really want to do it together.
I want to do octuplets.
No octuplets.
It's better to buy two.
We'll make four molecules, right?
We're going to do octuplets.
I wanted to do octuplets.
It's more popular to buy two.
Just like that? This is...
Yes.
I knew it. But it's a way for adults to enjoy Disney.
That's good.
You said you've never had a drink at Disney.
I drank for the first time.
I was so happy.
I hope they drink beer soon. At Disney.
I can't drink it.
I want to drink it.
Because beer at Disney is the best beer.
I see.
It's the best.
I want to drink it.
I can't wait to drink it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I can't wait.
Is that how it's going to be?Something like that?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to posting it on my Instagram afterwards.
There are so many.
I think it's because it's all girls, and if you go with 8 girls, they'll be taking pictures almost the whole time.
That's true.
They're taking pictures.
Arline is the most cute taking pictures.
And so is everyone else.
I think I take a lot of pictures when I go with my friends, my classmates, or friends of the same generation,
I don't think I can compete with young people.
But Arline would take 3 or 4 pictures and then just snapping away.
We are already taking three or four shots.
We're taking dozens of pictures.
When we were finally done shooting, Aaryn asked if we could go,
I'm sorry, don't take another video.
Sorry, don't take another video, because the video will start.
Sorry, you'll have to upload it.
I'll be back in a little while.
I thought that was pretty cool, since everyone was filming.
But didn't you take a lot of pictures?
I took a lot of pictures.
It's hard to choose.
So many. That's what makes it fun.
You return them to me afterwards, right?
That's right.
I'll give it back. For sure.
For sure.
I can't believe Harry and Disney.
At this moment...
It's so chopped up.
I had to record it.
It's important.
It was fun like that, wasn't it?
It was fun.
So, uh, you said you're looking forward to the video?
Yes, please look forward to it.
There are lots of cute videos.
Okay, I understand.
You can look forward to them.
Okay, next?
Yes.
Next!
Yes!
Here's a picture of Arin and Moeka leaking.
They are leaking so much!
The sunlight is also nice.
The fact that I'm at Disney with Arin is just too much.
It's a treasure.
They are so cute.
It leaks when it's sunny.
I knew it was Disney.
It was great, wasn't it?
If I told you how cute they were, you would have said it was a dance hall, right?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to leave anything out without permission, right?
I really don't.
I don't have many pictures of me in the light.
That's funny.
I did it. I'm really happy about this.
It's so cute.
Disney country is amazing.
We went to various photo spots together.
Yes, yes.
But I guess Hana-chan and I had time to take pictures, too.
This attraction is open now.
Yes, pretty much.
Hana-chan has been taking care of the time allocation.
She's doing a great job.
She's trying to take pictures in a bright position.
But it's still raining, so it's impossible now.
I really felt like I could rely on her.
It was really nice.
He said, "Let's go to the restroom so we can take a picture," and he took everyone's bangs with him.
That's true.
That's right.
There's a restroom over there.
But the bathroom here is too small for the mirror.
Let's go to a bigger place.
That day was really smooth. The whole day.
There was no time.
I've never been around in one day.
The best way to appeal to Disney lovers is the location of the restroom.
I knew it.
If you go around quickly, you can see the restrooms.
There it is.
I'll turn this way, though.I'll turn this way.
I know where the bathroom is.
That's the point.
It's one of the points that make people around you think you like Disney.
It's nice for the girls, isn't it?
It's nice, isn't it?
They tell me about the wide mirror.
He does that. And there, too. Make sure.
You really need to know where the bathroom is.
It's important.
And the location of the vending machines.
Yes, that's for sure.
I guess there are a lot of people who don't know where the vending machines are.
That's for sure.
It's in a rather hidden place, isn't it?
You can't find it.
When I went there alone, there were so many vending machines. There were no vending machines.
Really?
Yes, there are.
I thought it was great, but it was only for about 30 minutes.
Oh, no.
I'm sure they're selling it to everybody.
It was wagwag.
Wasn't that amazing, too?
He knew where to find the char-supe. Genius.
He knows where the char-spot is.
The story of Chacepo.
Ichikawa-san's chassupo story is amazing.
Really.
Chassupo is a place where you don't destroy the world of Disney.
It's placed in a brown part of the tree so as not to destroy the Disney world.
The char-spot is always blue, but
Disney's chargers are always blue, but this one is brown.
But it's brown.
So as not to destroy the world of Disneyland.
I couldn't find it.
Where is it? It's like, "Where is it?
You should bring your own.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
It's been a problem at Amefura.
And yet they didn't bring it to Disney.
I was using Aaryn's final.
Right.
I took it.
People don't know what a char-supo is.
You don't know what a char-supo is?
They don't know what Chacepo is.
I knew it.
What I had them do this time was to go to Disney with me.
I had a char-spot.
Did Aaryn know about it too?
I didn't know what a "char-spot" was.
I didn't know it was called a "char spot" until I heard Yuzu say it.
I learned that a charge spot is called a charspot.
You know, a mobile battery.
Oh, yeah.
A spot that provides carrirail is called "charspot".
It's called a charspot.
It's a tea spot.
Peace pong.
It's become "peace pong.
And they take pictures.
I take pictures, I wait, I use apps.
My phone's battery is going down a lot.
It's going down a lot.
But it's all gone.
The show.
I wanted to do Jumbo Mickey.
I missed the Jumbo Mickey show, too.
Has anyone ever won a show?
I don't know.
But I don't want to be 44 and win one of them.
I don't want to do that.
I'm worried about being in the way.
I went with about 8 people.
I wanted to see Jumbo Mickey.
I wanted to dance as much as your sister.
I'm sure he'll stand out.
Sounds like fun.
What's wrong with that girl over there?
I'm going to put in a little wave or something.
It's a little bit better.
The corners are different.
Just this one corner.
That's for sure.
That's a lot of people.
They'll stop now.
If only they would stop.If only we could stop.
Mobile batteries, too,
There are so many ways to do it.
Like mobajou, right?
Some people call it "Mobaba.
Mobile battery?
Some people are laughing all the time.
Stop it already.
They started acting weird again.
Stop it. Do it in the back.
Jambolimickey.
What?
If you're going to do it, do it in a way that everyone can understand.
You can do it.
Generally.
Is that okay?
That hurt.
Don't do it just once.
You can do the wave to Jumbo Mickey.
I want to see it so bad.
It's Mamoue's delivery.
It's not Mamoue, or he's doing it.
They don't know yet.
They know.
They've got plenty of time.
They call it a mobile battery.
That's right.
Mobile battery hand?
It's not a mobile battery.
We need a charger.
You call it a charger?
We need a charger for the most part.
It's called "mochiju" or "mobaju", isn't it?
What is that?
A mobile battery or a portable charger.
Mobajyu has a name.
That's great, Akashis.
That's great.
Is it like that?
Yes.
Then, next to the picture you are thinking of, here it is.
And here it is.
Yay!
That's great.
I made it.
One set.
I'm on it.
I knew it. Eight people can occupy one car.
We can occupy it.
Six thousand people.
We all took on the challenge, didn't we?
I wonder who chose this one.
What is this pose?
I want you to guess once.
Sure.
What is this pose?
It's a pose about waves.
It's true that everyone looks a little different.
You must have practiced a lot.
Yes, I did.
I practiced a lot while we were standing in line.
I practiced a few times, like the small part where you fall off.
I fell about three times.
On the small platform.
I practiced on that small platform too.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
What's the big one?
It's hit.
I'm hit.
That's great.
It's better than when we stopped.
That's good.
But I didn't expect it to be so obvious.
That's great.
How do you know?
You all answered correctly.
Yes, you did.
What's the right answer?
It's the circle to the wave pose.
That's great.
What? What is it?
It's the future.
The future.
Circle of the Waves.
Does everybody know about that?
What's that?What was that?
What was that?
Wait a minute.
Did you see that coming?
What happened to everyone overall?
What was that? Was that the loop to the wave?
I'm surprised.
You're not going?
Everyone.
Most of us heard it, so it was a surprise.
What?
Wait, maybe there's a loop to the wave.
What's that? The loop to the wave.
Where is it?
No, no, no.
They all look different.
They're all the same.
Maybe they were all the same.
A little bit.
I was the only one who noticed.
Is everyone different?
I don't know.
I thought about it, and it was a pose like this.
It was like this.
Yes, it was.
Not spread out.
There's a guy with a great laugh.
That's, you know, future.
Future flower.
Flowers of the future.
Yes.
Future flower.
You've made up your mind. I've made up my mind.
Yes, we did.
We all decided to make a "Namihe-esque" pose.
Namizui also looks like Namihe.
MC.
But there is one person who didn't do the last pose of Minayuru Ohki,
So let's start with the person in front.
Front row.
A little bit in the front row.
Can't you put me in the front row?
A little front row.
You shouldn't be in the front row. I know, right?
It's just...
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
The first one.
I made a mistake.
I don't feel any remnants.
You should try harder.
This pose, we are.
Our palms are like this.
They're not going to do it anymore.
They have zero motivation.
We're not going to do it.
But Ernie knew. I did this, didn't I?
I was doing it.
But after the fall.
It was hard.
It was difficult.
It was pretty much 2 seconds after the fall, wasn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Pretty much.
And it was only noon at that time. We were there relatively early,
We wanted to protect our hair.
You can do this right after you take a picture like this,
They make you practice this kind of thing?
Like this.
The water is high.
Great water.
It's the best.
There's a lot of it.
It's the most expensive.
But this is also significant for the lumplings.
That's right.
If you keep this pose until the very end,
I was holding this pose until the very end, and then the guy in front of me started to goof off, and I thought, "What? I thought, "Oh, no, all the water's coming.
It was a super water-drawing.
I was the only one who got soaked. From noon.
I was soaked with champagne.
I don't know. Chi-chan and Rumpan were soaking wet.
Chi-chan was probably throwing it down.
Chi-chan and Rumpan were all wet.
It was pretty good. We were all having fun.
This is because the water would probably come about two seconds after the picture was taken,The water will probably come about 2 seconds after the picture is taken,
So, if you just squat down at the moment the picture is taken, you won't get hit by the water.
I was a little concerned that Chi-chan and Rumpan didn't like it, but they kept standing up.
That's not good. I thought it would be a little lower.
It's gone down a lot.
I didn't make it in time.
I got all wet.
It was fun.
You look like you had a great time.
We didn't do it right,
I'm really sorry we didn't do it right.
I'm so sorry.
Aaryn is a girly-girl.
I thought he was trying to do it.
But if you think about it, Yuzu and Hanyu are raising their hands and pretending to go over there.
He is raising his hand.
They are doing their best.
They are too good.
But Rumpan and Hanyu are good.
I want to see a close-up of Hanyu's face.
Hanyu's face.
It's terrible.
It's all Kapilai.
This is Japan, isn't it?
Japanese photo.
But the lumplings don't fall apart too much.
Seriously.
It's amazing.
Cute loompan.
Why are they so cute?
Why such 16 characters?
He still has a little bit of bangs.
Yay.
Too much contrast, you know?
I really don't like it.
The tension.
It's not good.
I really don't like it.
He's like a prince.
On the contrary, he looks fake.
His face.
On the contrary, it looks fake.
It's like, "No, it's not like that.
It's deliberate.
It was deliberate.
No, he was desperate. They were desperate.
They were really noisy all the time.
They were really loud.
Gimme a break.
Cake, what's wrong?
Oh my God, it's so bad.
I thought it was a really loud ski tone.
I really thought so.
It was the first time I've ever seen someone yell "gimme gimme gimme!
The little kids behind Yuri were also yelling.
They were like 4 or 5 years old.
Boys.
They were getting excited.
I heard a high-pitched voice that sounded like "cawing.
I hear a raised voice that I can hear.
Maybe the timing is off.
A little early.
A little later.
Before the climax.
It doesn't mean it's off.
I yell before they come, so when they don't come.
When they don't come, I say, "C'mon!" and the people behind me say, "C'mon!
It's like, "I like it.
It's fun for me.
It was really loud.
I had a lot of fun at the start of the tour.
I thought, "I want to be someone who can get excited at the start of the tour like that.
I was like, "You know, even if I go to the start of the tour
I can get on the bus in 5 to 10 minutes.
I was in a position where I could get on the bus in 5 to 10 minutes.
That's not true.
Is that so?
First thing in the morning.
My first morning ride.
It was kind of dark in front of my eyes.
I wondered what was going to happen.
It started moving in 3D.
I was so impressed.
I was moved.
I was super impressed.
It was fun.
After that, I saw Hari-chan's first performance and that made a big impression on me.
I had a great impression of him.That's what made a great impression on me.
I mean, you know, to the next ride.
I was so impressed that Ary was so excited to be on the next ride.
Ary said, "I don't want to go on the Harimat alone.
I was always saying that I didn't want to go on the Harimat ride alone.
Harimat was the one next to the starting tour.
If we were riding like this, it would be noisy all the time.
I was so noisy all the time.
I don't know where his voice was coming from.
But I got on the end of the train.
I was surprised. I was at the very end.
And it was so loud.
I thought I was right next to the next one.
I guess you can see the very end.
I wonder how loud it is.
There's a master with a face like this.
Help me. It's too loud.
Oh, no. Oh no.
I'm going to get so mad.
It was fun.
That's how I feel.
I have some regrets about this.
It turned out great.
It was a little frustrating.
I'd like to try again at night.
That's how it ended.
I'm sorry about that.
Next photo.
Coffee cup!
So cute.
We all got on the coffee cup, didn't we?
We rode on it.
So cute!
It's not easy to get 5 cups from outside with friends.
That's true.
Because they all ride on the same cup.
That's right. That's why it's rare.
That's true.
It's only because we went in a big group.
But we had dinner at Alice's, right?
Yeah.
Oh, man, we only had a little bit of time left.
That's when there was about an hour left, right?
That's right.
Say an empty coffee cup.
It was right in front of me.
We ate with a lot of gusto, didn't we?
It was a lot of food.
Which one did you eat?
But I said, "Let's go," and I did.
I felt really sick.
But I checked. Before I got on.
I want to turn it as much as I can.
I want to turn.
If you don't want to spin, let's get on another one.
I'm sure they'll be very concerned about it.
I told you that in my memory. You said so.
You said it would be fine. Everyone was fine.
I was so excited when I got on the train that I turned one leg already, but after I got off, I felt sick.
My eyes were spinning.
That's right. It was really like being in front of a pub in the middle of the night.
I saw it.
That's right.
The video after the show is really funny.
Do you have it? That cup of coffee.
Gib.
There's probably a video of it coming out.
I'm sure there is.
With Chi-chan,
Chi-chan and Aira were in trouble.
Moeko was also a giver, wasn't she?
That's right.
So, Moe-chan was sitting on the bench first.
She was sitting on the bench.
It was the shortest route.
We were so close.
Chi-chan was like this from the time we were on the train.
That's right. That's right. That's right.
Chi-chan was the worst.
There's Moeka sitting on the bench and everyone coming after her.
Oh no.
The first time I rode with Moe-chan.
Really?
If the others weren't there all the time.
I don't have a video, but I have a picture.
I have pictures.
In the video, Moechen stops Hana-chan's hand that she's turning so hard like this,
I'm sure Hana-chan will stop her too.
I won't let you stop me.
I'm glad.Good.
I'm a craftsman.
Moe-chan was fun.
My field of vision was just lines all the time. There was nothing but lines.
There were nothing but lines.
That's right. So much so that some people dropped out.
It turned.
I really think that Disney's coffee cups rotate a lot.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It spins really fast, doesn't it?
Usually, the person who spins the cup and the person who enjoys spinning the cup take turns.
In Oshima's case, he spins everything by himself. He enjoys it all by himself.
He is the best.
He is the strongest.
He comes around regularly.
I turn it myself.
I want to turn different people.
He is indeed a screener, but a craftsman.
He's a super craftsman.
It's amazing. Chii-chan, Ayurin, myself, and even Hariri were on the first ride,
I knew that my team and I were turning it in detail.
Yes.
I saw a video of Hana's team, and I was like, "This is it! Like this.
Like this! Like this.
A big one.
From the person who turns.
I thought, "I see.
I'm a driver from white.
He was really hardcore.
We went around so much.
So three of us wanted to take a break.
But three people wanted to take a break, so five of us got on one more time.
It was amazing.
It was really great.
We got really excited.
It was like if we didn't go next time after one ride, we wouldn't make it to the next attraction in time,
But I still wanted to go one more time, so I said, "Let's go! I said, "Let's go!
I went with a bang.
Let's go if you can go.
Everyone was so excited at that moment.
Let's go again?
Let's go! It was amazing.
It was amazing. It was not like that.
Even from the outside, that cup was really fast.
Really?
Really.
Centrifugal force is also important, so it didn't stick out a bit.
Yes.
What's that?
It was the wrong cup.
He asked me to take some kind of video, but I was too fast and I couldn't tell which cup it was.
It was one cup.
That's right. But four of us can only ride in one cup, so five of us.
We couldn't ride on one car.
So we split up and rode separately.
Yes, we did. We split up.
Ah!
This is the second time you rode together.
We broke up and got on.
Hey.
Who's that?
A little bit of a close-up.
What side do you want to go on?
I don't know. 5 is usually 2 or 3.
What's that?
Obviously?
It's like we're all in one car.
We're all in one car.
It's only visible.
Because Harichan is out in front.
If that's the case, he's out too much.
I see.
Hari-chan lost in a fight, so she had to ride alone.
That's right.
But you played rock-paper-scissors with him, didn't you?
Five of us.
But I couldn't lose because if I lost, everyone would be very considerate and ask me to play rock-paper-scissors-paper again,
So I decided to play fair rock, paper, scissors,
So we played rock-paper-scissors-paper,
But I decided to play fair rock-paper-scissors-scissors, and I lost.
I was the only one who lost,
We played rock-paper-scissors-paper three times,
Then we posed for a rock-paper-scissors-scissors pose.
I lost by myself.
I felt sorry for him.
I got over it by myself.
Really.
Haga-chan was the first to say that.
That's right. Haga was the one who started it.Yes. Haga started it.
We were talking about how it would be nice if we could get on in twos and threes, but then Haga suddenly said, "What?
Suddenly Haga said, "Well, if one of us loses in rock-paper-scissors-scissors, then..,
I'm sorry.
I'll be the first, huh? He said, "I'm sorry, I'm the first one.
In such a situation, the one who says it first loses, right?
That's right.
I thought for sure I was going to lose.
Then, I thought, "Surely, this position is going to lose, too.
Yes, that's true.
This position, too.
Really...I did it all by myself.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Harichan was really tired from turning it all by herself.
Tired Moemi.
Wouldn't it be nice if she said that herself?
So, while the three of us are waiting.
That's right.
Take a break.
The five of us.
Super chi-chan face.
Chi-chan.
It's not a dreamland face.
She's super cute.
She's cute.
I took this picture of her when she was riding on the train,
The eyes.
I love it.
He looks so happy.
He's so cool.
He's releasing centrifugal force. Right now.
Using centrifugal force.
When he's having fun.
Yuzu is so cute.
Yuzu is cute.
It's true that when Yuzu is in the position to turn.
I'm looking forward to seeing him spinning.
Hana's face.
It's a video screencap, but the cute part in the video.
Cute is this way this release.
The cutest and cute this at the highest level.
If nothing else too.
It is cute in this.
Cute in this.
The cutest moment.
Enjoying the flowers.
It's too loud.
I thought it would be nice to see a gorilla or something.
I've been around gorillas for a while.
Gorillas!
I heard their voices.
Videos? Even if it was a video taken by the group that didn't get on the bus,
When we bought our coffee.
It was really amazing.
The speed and the voices were amazing.
The more he showed, the more he was enjoying himself.
It was a lot of fun.
We shot it twice.
It was fun.
I wanted to go a third time.
I wanted to see who would stay until the end.
I really wanted to do that.
We did it on time, didn't we?
Let's do it next time.
Let's definitely do it.
From abandoned park to flat park.
I don't want to do it.
Wait. Ever since the park closed.
Ever since the park closed.
How long have you been here, boss?
He's always been here.
They've been here forever.
They've been there for a long time, but they seem to be okay.
If only they'd give us some food,
This happens every time.
I want to try it.
The way advanced people have fun.
I'm pretty advanced.
Next.
Day event.
Everyone celebrated when we ate dinner.
It's his birthday.
It's Ali's birthday.
That's right. It was a little before his birthday.
It was the beginning of June.
Everyone is going to celebrate with the next picture.
So they start celebrating.They celebrate from so.
They bought me a cake.
Cute.
I didn't notice that at all.
We thought about it. Us.
Meeting among us,
What if Aaryn starts saying she wants to stop by here for lunch in the morning?
We had a subject inside.
From what I remember,
Like Hana-chan had lunch at Hana-Alice's place.
She said she would put in a natural.
I told her.
Let her feel your mood.
And then say it's okay.
But you know, to have dinner with everyone,
I thought we should have a meal where we can all sit together.
It's nice. Alice's place is spacious.
Then everyone bought a cake and congratulated me.
They congratulated me.
I was so happy. I didn't even notice.
Everyone was talking about it.
Rumpin started off by saying, "Arin, it's almost your birthday, so let's do something.
He said, "Let's do something.
I knew we'd have to play against each other.
A match, huh?
First of all, I talked to Hana-chan, who knows a lot about Disney.
She came to me with a line game.
What if she's the type of person who doesn't go to restaurants?
Right.
What if he's the smoth type?
What if he's the type who won't go to restaurants?
That's everyone. Adorction life.
I'm surprised. I haven't ridden like that in a long time.
What?
What? Why?
She said. Normally I would have ridden slower, but with Hana-chan there, it was amazing.
But you controlled it a little bit, didn't you?
Even so, it was a little less.
Eat, ride, eat, ride.
It was definitely in order.
That's for sure.
But there was also talk about the Pirates of the Caribbean luxury course restaurant,
Wait a minute. That wasn't a place we were allowed to go yet.
We talked about how expensive it would be, and they said, "No, you can't go there.
We were like, "No, we can't. We'll take a bath in this.
I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't do it.
I can't go in there with the Caribbean voice laughing.
No, because it makes my stomach cold.
It's true, the first time I saw a pirate in the Caribbean.
I don't know which one it is.
I thought it would ruin the atmosphere.
But I was happy. Thank you.
I'm glad. It was a great success.
Can you put it back? Take a picture.
It's like a press conference. Every time.
Everyone take a picture.
You look so happy when you're taking pictures.
Really.
They're so cute.
Every time, every time. I'm so embarrassed.
I want them to take a picture of me with the cake, too, so I ask them to take a picture of me, but I don't want to take a picture by myself.
I want to take pictures of everyone.
Arline, please look at me.
And then they start taking video.
I'm not sure if it's a press conference or not, but people are taking pictures of me every time.
I was surprised to see someone nearby peeking in to see what the press conference was about.
We all came out together.
It says "Lambasting" on it.
Such a happy fanbeating.
That's amazing. It's Daikin and Sugiko.
The chosen one.
We have to load up on Sugiko.
Because there are 8 of us. They've been chosen.
It's like a fan who piled up tens of thousands of dollars.
He's piling up a lot.
They're piling it up.
A premium off-line meeting.
Too premium.
It's like this.
It was fun.
And next.
It's nighttime.
It's nighttime, isn't it?
That's a great picture.
Aira took it.
In the blink of an eye.
I took it.
You take pictures in the daytime?
You take pictures in the afternoon?
It's tiny.I'm tiny.
I feel like I'm the only model.
It was amazing.
Moeka and I were walking together from the very back of the line,
I thought I looked so youthful in the back of the line.
I felt so happy.
I called Aira and she posed for a picture like this, so I snapped a quick shot.
So cute.
It's so bright.
It's a beautiful picture.
Very beautiful.
Where is this going?
This is the Revenge Splash Manten.
We were a little bit unworthy of clearing it for a period of time.
Thank goodness.
We need to get there as soon as we're on the second coffee cup ride.
It's closing.
It's going to close.
But if we get in line, it's ours.
There was a chance that they might be closed, so I wouldn't be able to get in line.
That was a bit of a gamble,
But somehow we managed.
We were just in time,
The next person after us was the last, right?
That's right. That was the end.
It was really last minute.
We just barely made it and got our revenge.
Here is the picture.
Oh, this is it.
That's it.
The fireworks started while we were waiting in line.
It was the best position.
It was a great place.
When we first saw the fireworks, we wondered which way the fireworks would go.
We all thought they were going to go up toward Cinderella Castle, but they were going to go up behind it.
It's totally different.
What's that? That's the best position.
But it's easy to see how beautiful it is in this picture.
Fireworks and smoke.
Who took this picture?
Oh, what's that?
This is my senior.
Senior.
That's senior Lungpan.
It's a video of him.
A screenshot?
It's not a screenshot.
What's going on?
Chloe, you might not understand at all.
It's the moment when there are a lot of people in the picture.
I told him we all saw it together.
But to see fireworks with this group.
This was the first time I saw them.
I hadn't seen fireworks since then.
I was happy to see them again so soon.
But there is someone who took beautiful pictures of the fireworks.
Next.
I love this one.
The skill of the live-ribble.
Isn't it so good?
It's so good.
The balance of the 4000th anniversary.
With balloons.
This is the most beautiful shot I've ever seen.
It's so beautiful.
It was a time of youth, wasn't it?
It was like that. Standing in line while watching the fireworks.
We rode it, didn't we? Scrash Manten.
I wonder if this is the video you have.
You changed your pose next time, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Please give this one too.
What is this pose too?
Can you guess what it is?
Here is the photo.
What's this?
You can do it.
Super beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
He's doing his best. You're doing great.
I'm glad. I'm really happy.
Revenge has succeeded.
It's good.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Amazing.
It's great.
It's coming, it's coming.
All they say is, "It's coming, it's coming.
It's coming, it's coming.It's coming, it's coming.
They're coming, they're coming.
You're getting the message.
What is this pose?
What is it?
What is it? Mr. Ichikawa.
They are flags.
They are different.
It's different.
I will definitely put it out as much as I can.
I will definitely give it my all.
No?
This is Prime Minister Omae.
You are Prime Minister Omae, aren't you?
It's Omae.
Prime Minister Omae.
What do you think? I said, "What are we going to do?
This is what happened.
I think A-nin said "Prime Minister Omae," right?
That's right.
I said.
We'll do it like this, with everyone in super pose.
Where is good?
Where is good.
There are a lot of poses like this or like this, right?
Surely.
That's what Ichikawa-san said.
I was wondering if there was a pose that would be easy to understand.
I had an idea.
So I asked him to do it.
This was a successful revenge.
I might have just left. Even after the bangs and all that.
But maybe it was because people didn't care.
How many people would you like to see with the door up?
Don't do that. That's not good.
Let's start at the top, on the right.
What face?
I love it!
You got me. You got it.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm really serious.
I'm really serious about this.
Of course not.
I'm really serious.
I do remember what we talked about.
I remember.
The actress from Ohno at the mass convention. Like, we're all going together.
Let's get it together.
Let's go together until the last minute.
That's the face of Woo at the convention.
It's not Woo.
It's not big.
It's amazing. You like it.
No, no, no.
It doesn't matter.
I'm sure. It's something different.
It's not a mass convention.
It's like Shaqing.
That's for sure.
It's cute.
I'm not a screamer. I'm the kind of person who really doesn't want to ride,
But when I do go on a ride, I have to do the "sue" part when I fall off.
Then my stomach gets a little unstable.
Oh, it's unstable, isn't it?
I have this face in all the pictures of me screaming.
I do it every time. I make a "Sue" face every time.
I make this face every time.
Breathing out face.
That's right.
I'm the only one who does it in Voight.
My hands are so tense.
This is funny.
He's really serious.
The person on the left has the same face as before.
Same face.
The black eyes are really scary, aren't they?
I used the same material only for the face.
A cat in the dark.
I'm sure of it.
I'm very serious too.
Oh my God.
Isn't it pretty scary? It's stopped.
Your kalsurenpang is so cute.
And he has bangs.
He has bangs.You have bangs.
That's amazing.
One person couldn't do it earlier.
Aira-san.
The two of them are doing it right.
They're cute.
You're doing it right.
You two were cute last time too.
That's right.
I have no comment.
No comment.
I'm skipping it.
I don't like them because they're cute.
Aira-san says she succeeded.
The way she won.
She's cute because she's Aira.
Because she can't fail.
Because there's no end in sight. She ended up in the back.
They ended up in the back.
The first row is pretty far down, isn't it?
I'm falling.
They were saying, "It's falling," as they worked hard.
Aira's bangs are too high.
It's like it's at an angle.
I don't like it.
I don't want to get angry.
I can't go home.
I did my best.
There won't be a next time. I won't be able to line up again.
You look like you did your best.
You did your best.
We all put in a lot of effort.
We all put a lot of effort into it.
It's funny.
Next picture.
I'm soaking wet.
I took this picture of everyone afterwards.
It's great.
They are soaking wet.
I said, "That's enough.
I'm just going in.
So the bigointment was a success.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I'm tired just thinking about it.
We rode a lot, didn't we?
We really rode.
We rode Baymax, too.
I see.
We stopped on the way to Big Thunder and stopped quite a bit.
And it stopped at an angle.
It stopped for about 5 minutes.
I really hated my nose. My nose at that time.
Who was next to me?
It was someone other than me.
My nose suddenly stopped.
Wait a minute.
I can't talk.
You're funny.
Say something.
What's going on?
What's with the marriage?
There was a guy standing in line.
When we stopped, I started doing this thing about how it would be cool if I was the boyfriend and this guy was the girlfriend.
I started talking about how it would be cool if I was the boyfriend and she was the girlfriend.
We started talking.
What was that all of a sudden?
He was saying to Loompa, "It's going to be okay.
There was someone behind him, right? People you can see.
Everyone is on their way.
He suddenly started talking.
What are you doing?
I thought we were leaving soon, so I was waving at the people in line, saying how cool it was like this.
The train stopped for about 5 minutes.
It was so cool.
Hana-chan is worried about me, but it's not like she can move me.
It's okay.
I'll be like this for about 5 minutes.
It's like I'm stuck here.
That's not cool.
I hated it.
I know, it was super uncomfortable.
See you later.
Also, that was fun. The teeth at the beehive in Splash.
Oh.
That was really interesting.
The white ones in the dark.
With the cable light.
It's not glowing.You're not shining.
Among everyone else.
It's just glowing there.
It's supposed to be super white.
It's just before the fall, so it's too messy.
Falling down.
We were all together.
It was really fun.
We were so excited about every single thing.
Yes, we were.
Well, I guess that's the end of the pleasantries.
Can you tell already?
One more hour.
It's already over.
That was quick.
I thought we'd go bowling at Atsuka.
What's that?
It's true.
I made a reservation, but it's already been an hour,
We're done.
It's over.
Even though we're going bowling.
If you have any questions, I'll answer them.
Sure.
I'm curious.
Did you find anything?
Did something happen? I'm sure I'll answer.
But what you were asking so much about earlier was, did they ever find out? I asked him,
Oh, you mean the members of Namie Women's 8 Union?
Surely.
They didn't say, "Are you Namie? They didn't say, "Are you Namie?
No, they didn't. I was pretty conspicuous, so I thought they would.
I thought they would say, "Are you Namie-san? I thought I would be asked, but I was not told "Are you Namie?
I was not told.
But you were wearing an Adidas backpack,
But I was wearing an Adidas backpack.
Yes, they did.
There was a pair wearing Chums backpacks,
They were walking right in front of us.
They were all wearing Adidas backpacks! He was walking right in front of me.
They seemed to be talking a lot.
Should I tell them what I want? I should tell them what I want?
Hari-chan was so antsy.
No, I don't want to.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's fine if he notices, but is he coming to me? It's coming to my hand.
It's funny, all of a sudden.
The people who carry Adidas backpacks might know who you are,
Shut up.
I'm serious.
I cried.
And then there was Isla... she got rough with me.
What, what, what?
And it wasn't a Japanese guy.
Ayla was roughed up by a Korean guy.
Seriously? When?
When Yuzu was timing the chums.
We were all there, and he was talking to Ira,
I'm sorry.
I want to be your friend.
You're cute.
Cute.
He's cute.
He was cute.
But I didn't tell you.
I didn't tell him.
There was.
There was, wasn't there?
Yes, there were times.
Yes, it did.
It's not easy to pick up girls at Disney, is it?
It might be amazing.
It's rare, isn't it?
There's no such thing as Disney.
It's a dreamland.
It's amazing.
How can you be so sure?
I've never met him.
In this day and age.
Yes, you're right.
But when I did meet him, he was playing with two girls, and she came with two boys,
If I said, "Let's go around with the same four people," there would still be banter.
Only one out of eight.
It was difficult.
He was a type 5.
And when I asked for help, no one looked at me.And when I asked for a little help, no one looked at me.
It didn't happen.
They didn't.
Everyone turned their backs to me.
Everyone made eye contact with everyone.
What did we eat?
Oh, but we all ate something in the morning... that omu-rice we shared at Roland's restaurant.
It was so good because someone was late and we weren't talking.
Someone was late so we waited for them at Roland's restaurant.
I had bibimbap, Halima had the one with Arin.
Hamburger and omelette. I thought so too.
What did you have, Alfa?
My dad had Little Creedman's. He'd never had it before.
What did you eat? I ate with Yuzu.
A little late, a little late, even though the three of us were late
I'm sorry. What's going on with the rain bath?
I called. They said we'd all be up in the morning.
That's sweet. That's sweet.
I asked Hana to call because I wasn't sure I'd be able to get up the day before.
I did, but I overslept because I woke up when Hana called.
The first time she didn't wake up, I called her around 6:00, she didn't wake up, and I thought it was over.
Then I called her again a little later and she just woke up.
I just woke up! The Orange group is late in the comments!
Oh no, no, no! Orange is late!
Please stop wearing orange. I get called that every time.
But we waited and waited and waited while we ate.
It was raining and the entrance was crowded.
Yes, yes, yes... Late Orange, stop it!
I made a mistake. And we ate popcorn and ice cream.
And we had popcorn and ice cream... and crème brûlée cholos. They were delicious.
Meat rolls? Meat rolls? - Laurie, I had the meat rolls.
I had a meat roll Laurie. Oh, that was good, too. Potatoes.
Oh, fries. Oh, fries. Like cheesy fries.
Like cheesy bacon and potatoes. They were good. They were so good.
But that's it? But, you know, I probably ate the whole time.
And crepes, right? Crepes... they were good. I ate them all the time.
Oh, at the cafe. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We ate at the restaurant again, but Arline's schedule didn't work out for us to go to Disney.
Our Disney dates didn't work out at all, but Aaryn was able to negotiate with our manager.
But Aryn was able to negotiate with our manager, and our manager asked if we could go to Disney, but it was a little hard to ask for time off.
I mean, it's kind of hard to ask.
I'm a sucker for a bad idea, and if I don't have any plans, I'm always quick to put in a good word.
I asked him once, out of the blue... and I just put it in the pen.
I was still pissed. I was so scared. I was so scared.
I can't say it a second time.
Except for Amehura, we agreed to do it on that day... and Namin from Amehura, if it's okay with Ori... the manager.
And then, Nami from Amehura, if Ori was okay with it...
They were all around the cell phone...
You were taking some kind of video, weren't you?
You were filming? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I really wanted to say that, because Arlie said it was really great.
I really wanted to say that.
He got us tickets right then and there. I just got them.
If you don't get in right away, I'll forget about you.
Arlie's line was so cool. We have to open it.
I wrote something like, "I'll do my best." He said he'd give me a whole day, even if it's light.
We can do the lesson in the morning at Maihama.
So we'll have a lesson at Kana Rinkai Park.
At the park? They'll do it in the park.
You can come as you are.
The flowers are done.
We talked a lot.
It was pretty pointless.
I was nervous, wasn't I?
I was extremely nervous.
It was real.
I was so nervous.
I was scared.
Because I was really hesitant to call.
It didn't come out.
I didn't answer, and I thought, "It's over.
When I looked at everyone's faces afterwards, they were all bright red.
Arin's face was red, too.
I was so nervous.
He said he would call the manager.
Sure.
Certainly.
He didn't pick up once and I had to wait for him to pick up,
I had to go home and call him back.
What was that? I would be asked, "What was it?
You have to make sure to call both the phone number and the phone number on the line.
You have to tell them.
He said it was okay at the time, but when I saw him later, he was still mad at me.
I had Aaryn tell him.
I didn't want him to tell me.
What if he gets mad? I said, "What if he gets mad at me?
The next time I saw him, I said, "Thank you very much.
We talked about it for a while. I was like, "What if?
Nothing happened.
A phone call from a manager is really nerve-wracking, isn't it?A phone call from a manager would really make me nervous.
You should go on line as much as you can.
Please don't call me.
We were at Disney, souvenirs, this is the manager, this is the manager.
I already appreciated it.
Not buying them all together, but one for each of us.
Thank you very much.
There's been talk about buying a catsuit once, probably.
To the manager.
Let's go buy a catsuit together.
Here it is!
There it is! There it is!
This is it.
It's a circle.
But this is it,
Movie?
Buy a ticket.
He's choosing a catsuit.
He's cutting it big.
Not this size.
Not this one.
We're sitting on our butts when we listen to you.
This is the catsuit when we're choosing.
We can choose the threads for the catsuit.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
Yuzuka and Kneeling down too.
It was amazing.
Ahhh babe.
It was so exciting.
It was fun.
But you've got to be a little more soba.
Negotiate.
But I want to go to the next C.
I want to go!
I want to go.
I want to go to C in a little while.
Let's work hard every day.
I'll do my best.
Let's work hard so that we can get snacks, too.
So, now that an hour has already passed, let's end with a final announcement,
I'll end with a final announcement.
Okay.
Then, let's have some announcements.
First of all, here's the announcement.
The girls are going to perform "Tsumiai no Sakura Nagashi" (Cherry Blossom Float),
We have just released a new song,
It is available on various services, such as Sportify and Apple Music,
It is available on various services, such as Sportify, Apple Music, and so on.
Yay!
I heard that a lot of fans are listening to it,
I've been getting a lot of comments from fans saying they're listening to it and liking this part,
It's a great song.
It's a really good song.
It's refreshing.
I hope you will listen to it while paying attention to the lyrics,
Please download it.
Next!
What's AIDS?
Official goods with you again
It is a decision to start self-ordering!
Yay!
The sales start date for this one is Monday, June 19 at 20:00
Mail order site of the goods,
Arue Shoten, a mail order site for official goods.
This is the merchandise that we sold at the concert the other day.
These are some of the goods that were sold at the recent concert,
Some of them are inner rings, towels, T-shirts, and so on,
T-shirts,
The T-shirt we are wearing today is one of them.
We are wearing it now.
We also have wristbands,
Please use them to show off your live performance.
Yay!
It's good for summer too, isn't it?
It's true.
It's really cool.
It's big, so you can use it a lot.
It's super cool.
I recommend it.
Yes, I do.
Please come.
Please come on June 19.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow night at 8:00 p.m.
Yes, please. Please do.
Yes. Please.Yes, please. Please.
Please.
Come on, I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Next!
This is a little bit about me,
It's my production goods.
You can't hit this. The Irene Ball.
You can accept applications until 23:59 today.
This is the same mail order site.
It's on sale at Maybibis.
We are selling them.
We are accepting applications now.
If you are a golfer,
You can use it for golf,
Of course, a little gently.
It will help you hit when you putt or putt.
Like at the end of the game.
You can hit it gently.
Of course, it would also be cute if you display it,
Or a foot massage.
I think it would be nice.
I think it would be good,
I'm sure it would be great.
This Usualin in golf wear is very
Cute!
I think it's very cute,
Please consider it.
And now, I have one more announcement.
Oh~!
Our new 7-person version of the artist photo
We've taken it!
Yay!
I'd like to share it with the public.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
You want to see it?
Here it comes!
Yay!
So cute!
The other day, I took a photo wearing a new outfit that I unveiled at a live performance.
The eye-catchers are all so cute and well put together.
Cleaning!
Fresh cleaning!
Yes, I know. So, I'm sure our website will be changing from now on,
I hope you will like the artist photos here.
The bottom two on the right.
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop.
Don't stop. I'm hiding.
I'm not hiding.
It's huge.
You're not hiding.
I'm trying a little too hard, so it's on the bottom right.
But Yuko looks like she's cleaning.
She looks like a cleaner.
I decided on the face. She looks like she's cleaning.
It's a cleaning look.
I couldn't do her hair, but I did her face like a cleaner.
It's cute.
Lumia also has a cleaning face.
He has a cleaning face.
Everyone has a cleaning face.
Isn't it nice?
By all means, the people at Splash Mountain, you know?
It's really different.
It's Moe.
Please, this way. This is what we're going to do now, everyone.
Please do so.
And last but not least, the most important announcement.
The schedule for the next regular convention has been set.
Here is the schedule.
On Sunday, August 13th, we will be holding our regular convention in Haimachi.
It's summer. Everyone.
What does that mean?
That means...,
It's been a year since summer.
We're doing Splash.
Let's do Plus Mountain. Let's do Plus Mountain.
Let's do it.
More details will be announced as they become available,
We hope you will make your plans now.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for today's announcement.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was great.It was amazing.
It all happened so fast. But, I wanted to tell you that I went to Disney so I wanted to report it as soon as possible,
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I'm happy for sure.
I can finally post pictures.
I'm sure they will be posted on each of the Insta sites as soon as possible,
Please check it out.
Any announcements for everyone?
Yes, I have.
Okay?
Let's start with Ameflasi.
Amefrasi will have a release final at Raraport Toyohashi on the 24th of this month.
The time is from 12:00.
We are working hard to get 500 people to agree, so we hope you will all come and join us.
It is free of charge.
If you are coming for the first time, two shots are free.
This is where Ira got the buzz.
Is this it?
This is it. If you listen to the mini-album "Coffee," you'll enjoy this release even more,
Please listen to it if you like.
Please listen to it.
Are you okay? After that.
Yes, I'm fine.
You're OK?
Yes, I am. So, thank you all for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
Next regular meeting. I hope we can distribute it before then. That's quite a while away, isn't it?
We will let you know when it is decided,
We will let you know when it is decided, and we hope you will look forward to it as well.
So, thank you very much for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
After this, I would like to say a big thank you to all the people in my house, in my to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home
to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home, to those who are in my home
to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home, to the people in my home to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home
To those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home, to those in my home
is